Big Buck Bunny - Subtitle Test
This is a test subtitle for Big Buck Bunny
The video starts with nature scenes
You should see a forest and trees
Big Buck Bunny appears
Watch the butterflies
Beautiful outdoor scenery
The bunny is enjoying nature
Testing subtitle visibility
Change subtitle style in settings
Adjust size, color, and opacity
Multiple format support (SRT, VTT, ASS, TTML)
Subtitle caching enabled
ExoBoost Subtitle System
Switch between different subtitle files
Real-time style updates
Production-ready implementation
Thank you for testing!
Use Settings to customize appearance
Subtitle system demo complete!